The combat system of the war has
changed greatly with the times, and now
there are weapons such as fighter
jets and missiles that use high-tech.
However, the final stage of
the battle is still decided by
the ground battle, and military
guns still play a major role.
There are many types of
military guns, from large-scale to
small-scale, and there are
various ways to classify them.
In this video, we have classified the assault
rifle, the squad automatic weapon, the
so-called SAW, and the machine gun into three
categories based on the modern combat form.
The assault rifle is a
rifle supplied to each
soldier, and is now
simply called a rifle.
In order to be used at the
forefront of the ship, it requires
firm operation, high rate of
fire, and easy control during fire.
At the same time, ease of
maintenance is required, and it
is also a condition that
disassembly and cleaning is easy.
In addition, in order to be
supplied to all soldiers, high
productivity is required in order to
be able to produce a large amount.
Also, in modern combat models,
the vehicle is carried in parallel
with the driver and the helicopter,
so it has become an
important condition that
it is compact and
does not take up space.
The latest assault rifle of
FN is the FNC 5.56mm NATO,
and the FN FAL of the same
vehicle, which has already
been approved, has been
improved and scaled down.
It was completed in 1976.
The bottom part of the receiver
is made of an aluminum alloy.
The upper part is a
combination of press and steel.
In addition, the mechanism
is a rotary bolt-type locking
system that is suitable for
small and high-speed units.
It has been noticed as a new
assault rifle that has changed to the R.
It is official in Belgium,
Sweden, and Indonesia.
It is considered to be
adopted in many countries.
The latest assault rifle
of Heckler & Koch, G41.
It is designed to be strongly
aware of the US military's official rifle
and uses the M16 magazine, which
has become NATO official, as it is.
It is completed with the specs required for modern
assault rifles, such as the use of a bolt-forward
system that definitely sends ammunition into the chamber
and standardization of three-point burst control.
Currently, the Italian
Franchi company has
acquired the license,
and production has begun.
The American assault rifle M16A1
was completed by improving the AR10
to a small-scale version by the
Armalite company's friend Stoner.
In 1960, the American military officially
became the cause of the Vietnam
War, and later improved for the
Army, and the M16A1 was introduced.
A small action micro-locking lug that
uses a part of the launch gas directly,
and a body with a variety of
aluminum alloy and a plastic stock.
A new mechanism and
material drew attention.
This is the M16A2, which has evolved
in accordance with NATO's new policy.
And the M203 Grenade
Launcher, which fires a grenade.
This is the short model M16A2 Carbine,
which is designed for special forces.
It is 162mm in length and 800g
in weight from the original M16A2.
The M16 series is currently
used in more than 60 countries,
including the United States,
Canada, Israel, and the Philippines.
The latest Russian assault
rifle, the AK-74, was introduced
early in the Vietnam War
against the American army.
In 1974, Russian heavy-duty
designer Mikhail Karashnikov
developed the AK-47 as a base
and made the model smaller.
The AK-74 series short model
AKS-74U has the same mechanism as the
AK-74 and a foldable stock, and
the barrel size is 214mm shortened.
This is based on the AKM, the
AMP69 developed by Hungary on its
own, and it has the ability to
fire grenades in its original state.
The simple structure called
"Karashnikov System" common
to the AK series has high
durability and productivity.
It is currently used in many
countries such as Russia and Eastern
Europe as a representative assault
rifle of former socialist countries.
Let's compare the M16A1
5.56mm and the Russian AK74
5.45mm, which were the
official of the US military.
5.56mm, 5.45mm.
In the experiment, we used
a 25mm thick copper plate.
The 5.56mm bullet stopped at the 9th plate,
but the 5.45mm reached
the 13th plate and jumped out.
Next, we shot the clay.
It was slow, but the 5.45mm
bullet was penetrating.
The bullet head is easy
to deform, and even in
this experiment, it was
missing the upper part.
Even if it is the same type of bullet,
if the type of bullet is different,
Even for the same target, its properties
and performance change significantly.
There are many types of
ammunition, and each time a suitable
type of ammunition is selected
and used depending on the purpose.
"Irish Army Official Rifle L85A1"
It is based on the AR-18 rifle
designed by Eugene Stoner, and the
magazine is set to the rear of the
grip, which is called a bullpup style.
The Bullpup type is equipped
with a receiver inside the shoulder
stock to make it possible to assemble
the whole gun in a compact size.
It has many advantages such
as easy to control even while
on the train, and it is one
of the current assault rifles.
The L85A1 has this new concept
in the orthodox press-coated
body, and is finished with a
rifle with excellent durability.
Australia's Steyr AUG,
which has a futuristic form.
The stock and grip are integrated.
Most of the parts in the receiver
are made of special plastic,
and the magazine is
semi-transparent so that
the internal ammunition
can be confirmed.
The scope is integrated with the receiver,
with less crumple and a carrying handle.
Although it is a bullpup
type, the ejection port, which
releases the gun, can be
set to either left or right,
It also supports left-handed shooters.
Other than Austria, many
countries such as New
Zealand, Australia, and
Saudi Arabia are formalized.
The French military's official
assault rifle "Farmas" is equipped
with a bipod with excellent
stability that allows accurate aiming.
On the other hand, the
advanced design that supports
plastic is called the
"trumpet" from its appearance.
The G3 is a rifle equipped
with a unique system.
In the 1950s, in a research
facility in Seto in Spain,
a German engineer designed it as a base and
the Heckeler & Koch company completed it.
It has a unique blowback
system with a roller lock,
and it is characterized by its high
productivity by using a wide range of presses.
The G3's submachine gun version.
The US manufacturer specializing
in remodeling has aimed
to produce a submachine
gun with the greatest power.
This is a G3 with a 40mm grenade launcher.
It can also fire anti-personnel,
anti-tank guns, and anti-tank missiles.
The G3 has high achievements as an
assault rifle with a 7.62mm NATO bullet.
Today, more than 40 countries
in the world, including Germany,
Sweden, Portugal and more than
10 countries, have licensed this rifle.
The best seller of this rifle is FN-FAL,
which is the best seller of the Belgian FN.
FN-FAL is the best seller of
this rifle, because it is a reliable
rifle with an orthodox tilt-bolt
method and a reliable steel receiver.
In 1952, it became a
mass-produced rifle,
and it was sold mainly
in western countries.
Currently, it has been licensed in more
than 10 countries, including Belgium, the
United Kingdom, and the former British
Empire, and has been adopted in 36 countries.
G11, developed by Heckler & Koch
as a next-generation assault rifle.
The greatest feature of this gun,
which has a unique straight-line
shape, is that it fires a case-less
bullet that has no muzzle.
The case-less bullet itself
is light, and it has a great
advantage that it can carry
a large number of soldiers.
In addition, it does not need to
release muzzle, so even the bullpup
type also has the advantage of not
choosing the right arm of the shooter.
It has been noted as a weapon that
shows a new possibility for assault rifles.
Currently, tests have been repeated
in Germany and the United States.
The military gun has
experienced various forms
of combat and has
reached the present day.
Currently, the military
gun, which is classified in
various ways, is the origin of
two rifles and machine guns.
The rifle, which pursues
chain reaction ability, appeared
as a bolt action in the
second half of the 19th century.
Dreyse and Mosel completed
the modern rapid-fire rifle.
The short-action rapid-fire
rifle was improved and
continued to be used in the
First and Second World Wars.
In the Second World War,
many new guns appeared,
and the combat system
changed significantly.
The rifle also required the ability to fire
many bullets in a short period of time.
In this way, the sub-machine gun,
which pursued only the small-sized,
continuous performance, was completed
at the end of the First World War.
The sub-machine gun, which is representative of
MP-18, had a full-automatic continuous function,
but the range was short to use a pistol bullet,
and it was powerful only at close range.
During the Second World War, each country
produced various types of submachine
guns and became widely used by the general
public and improved for mass production.
At the end of the Second World War, Germany
developed the MP-43, which has a range that
is not inferior to a rifle and can be fired
like a submachine gun even in full automatic.
The modern assault rifle is a
prototype of this gun concept.
The appearance of MP-43 has
had a great impact on the later rifles,
and AR-10 was developed in the
United States and later improved to M16.
The early machine guns
appeared in the middle of
the 19th century in the
United States and Europe.
At the beginning of the First World War, these machine guns
were divided into small, small-sized anti-aircraft guns, such as
Schwarzlose and Vickers, for defense purposes, and MG 0815 and Lewis,
for small-sized attacks, and each began to follow its own path.
During the Second World War,
M1919 and MG34 of Browning were
used as the same gun for both
attack and defense purposes,
and the General Purpose
Machine Guns were used
to respond to vehicle-type
and anti-ship types.
On the other hand, light
machine guns have been further
lightweighted, with the development
of RIG-CHALEV and the RIG-99 type.
These compact machine guns are used
as support machine guns for each unit,
It became the prototype of the
modern "Squad Automatic Weapon".
It has a barrel of 7.62 mm FAL rifle
and is known as "FN LAR" as a SAW.
The mechanism is exactly the
same as the FAL, but the thickness
of the barrel part has been
increased to allow longer-term firing.
Furthermore, the bipod
and the back of the stock are
equipped with foldable shoulder
pads to improve accuracy.
It is in line with the
requirements as a SAW.
The FN LAR has the same
operation as the FAL, so many
countries are using it at
the same time as the FAL.
Just like the M16A2 LMG FN LAR,
which is based on the M16A2, the barrel
of the M16A2 rifle is strengthened
and the bipod is strengthened.
The top of the barrel is equipped with
a carrying handle, and the lower part
is equipped with a foregrip, which makes
it easy to shoot while moving forward.
In addition, a special magazine with
a capacity of 100 shots has also been
manufactured, which allows a greater
number of ammunition to be delivered.
It is currently used in the US Marine
Corps, as well as in El Salvador and Brazil.
The AK-74 is based on
the SAW model, RPK-74.
Like other SAWs, it has a bipod
with a longer barrel size than
the AK-74 and achieves a longer
range at a faster bullet speed.
It is equipped with a 15-round
magazine and a 45-round
plastic magazine with
15 rounds from the rifle.
In response to this, the
recoil spring and receiver
are strengthened to
enable long-term firing.
The RPK-74 uses rotary
bolts and uses the same
mechanism as the AK-74,
which operates at gas pressure.
Currently, it is used
mainly in Eastern European
countries, including
Russia and the AK-74.
For the trial of the U.S.
military, the FN developed the Minimi SAW.
It has been developed in a way that
makes the machine gun lighter and smaller.
It is different from other SAWs
that have enhanced the assault rifle.
The biggest feature
is that it can be put
together with the belt
link and the magazine.
The magazine uses 30 rounds of M16.
In addition, it is also possible to exchange
barrels with heat by long-term fire.
It is highly evaluated as a SAW that matches the current
combat form, and has been adopted in many countries,
including Belgium and the United States, and Japan's
Self-Defense Forces have decided to introduce it as the next SAW.
The modern machine gun can be used for various purposes
by replacing parts, and in addition to being used on the
ground, it is required that it can be used in a wide
range of areas, including vehicles, ships, and aircraft.
This is FN's general purpose
machine gun, FN MAG.
In the early 1950s, the
machine gun was introduced
as a 7.62mm NATO
bullet as soon as possible,
and it became the
bestseller in the market,
focusing on Western
countries along with FN FAL.
The ballast system is belt-linked.
The receiver with the steel plate is
equipped with a simple lock system.
The movement uses gas pressure.
The barrel is interchangeable.
Other than the standard ground model, various
variations can be developed, and more than
1.5 million units have been produced so far,
and more than 70 countries have adopted them.
The latest machine gun of Heckeler & Co.,
which uses a 5.56 mm NATO bullet, is GR-9C.
It is equipped with a unique dollar
locking system of Heckeler & Co.
and has a fixed scope
to improve accuracy.
The model, which has a
bright colored paint, is equipped
with a "C" for camouflage,
and is called the "GR-QC".
The belt-linked ballast system can be
used to replace parts, and the magazine for
the rifle can also be installed, and the
barrel can also be replaced with one-touch.
The M2 HMG, which fires
12.7mm large-scale bullets, is a
prototype designed by genius
machine inventor John M. Browning.
Later, improvements were made,
and the current style was born in 1933.
Up to now, more than 2 million
aircraft have been produced
in the type of vehicle, tank,
aircraft carrier, and so on.
It is adopted by the US
military and NATO countries.
It supports the high-techization
of systems and continues to
evolve by incorporating new
materials and manufacturing methods.
And no matter how diverse
the fighting form is, the
military gun does not change
to play an important role.
Guns of the World Vol.
3 Special Purpose Weapons
In this video, I will introduce some of the
special units used by the anti-terror police,
including submachine guns, sniper rifles, and
combat shotguns, as special purpose weapons.
Of course, the normal submachine
gun is the Silencer submachine gun.
Stirling L-34 MP5SD.
The P90 was developed to be a
military gun of a new category.
This is a video for the
first time in the Atashu
Case MP5, which is
exclusively for VIP protection.
Guns of the World Vol.3
Special Purpose Weapons
Guns of the World Vol.1 Handguns
In the first series, Handguns
features the Beretta 92F, Glock 17,
The latest 44 Magnum revolvers such
as Semi-Automatic Pistol and Smith &
Wesson M629 and Colt Anaconda, which
are now the most popular in the world.
From historical guns, special guns,
to full automatic machine pistols,
Guns of the World Vol. 1 Handguns,
which conveys the charm of the gun.